celebratinghome.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Celebrating Home Direct

This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how Celebrating Home Direct LLC and its affiliated brands, including CelebratingHomeDirect.com, Home & Garden Party, LTD, Celebrating Home, Penelope Ann, and Home Interiors ("CH Direct", "we" or "us") collects and processes the information that you share when you use this and any of our websites, including our mobile applications and related consumer services.

Before submitting information to the Service, please review this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing the Service, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you prefer that we not collect and process information about you, please do not provide it to us and do not access the Service.

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under 13. Where any such information is inadvertently collected, we will delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information please contact us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

### How do we protect visitor information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

For your convenience we may store your credit card information for more than 60 days in order to expedite future orders, and to automate the billing process.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **We use cookies to:**

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

 **If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled. It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. You will not be able to place an order with us.

### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.

### Google Analytics (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities, and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

We implement Google Analytics features that use Display Advertising information for Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, by going to the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). You can read more about the cookies used by Google Analytics advertising features, by going to the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

We use Google AdWords Remarketing to advertise celebratinghomedirect.com across the Internet, in particular on the Google Display Network. AdWords remarketing will display ads to you based on what parts of the celebratinghomedirect.com website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your web browser. This cookie does not in any way identify you or give access to your computer or mobile device. The cookie is used to indicate to other websites that "This person visited a particular page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

If you do not wish to see ads from celebratinghomedirect.com you can opt out in several ways:

  1. Opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting [Google’s Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated).
  2. Opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: [CalOPPA](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/).

 **According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

  * By logging in to their account

### Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?

It’s also important to note that we do allow third party behavioral tracking.

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

 **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email:

  * Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only those individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### CAN-SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **We collect your email address in order to:**

  * Send information, respond to inquiries and/or other requests or questions.
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

 **To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:**

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

 **If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails** , you can click the **“Unsubscribe”** link at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

### How to Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Celebrating Home Direct  
1070 Pumpkin Center Road  
Marshall, Texas 75672   
CustomerService@celebratinghomedirect.com  
(903) 935-4197
